ANKIT AGRAWAL

Contact Information

ABOUT ME

I am passionate person when it comes to programming. I am a coder, mentor with over 8 years of experience in web development field. I am responsible for implementing projects strategies that help developers to achieve their goals.

EXPERIENCE

Technical Director

Web Planet Soft March 2015 - Present

Team Leader Sep 2010 - Feb 2015

Vertax Web Technology

Php Developer Jan 2010- Aug 2010

IBTEDA Convergence Technology

EDUCATION

B.E. (C.S) 2005-2009

Rajasthan University JNIT, JAIPUR

Senior Secondary 2004-2005

Rajasthan Board M.N. Modern Public School,

Secondary 2002-2003

Rajasthan Board A.V.M School, Jaipur

Technical SKILLS

Language: Php

Frontend: Html, CSS, Js, jQuery,

Bootstrap

Framework: Cakephp, CI, Laravel,

CMS: WordPress, OpenCart, Phpfox, Boonex, Osclass, Joomla, Magento, Zen cart, Shopify, Ska

date

Database: MySQL, Sql Server 2005

Operating System: Windows, Linux,

Ubuntu

Web Server: Apache, Nginx

IDE: sublime, notepad++, bracket

FOLLOW ME

facebook/ankitagrawal.an twitter/ankit_an github/agrawalankit stackoverflow/users/1953016/ankit-agrawal

PERSONAL SKILLS

Creativity Hard Work Teamwork Team Management Project Management Marketing